Finding Aid for the Gladys M. Fitts Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Gladys M. Fitts Collection
1937-1986
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0141
.10 linear_feet
Biography/History
Gladys Moerner Fitts (1920 -----) received a Bachelor of Arts degree through the College of Arts and Science in 1941. She was a member of the A Capella Choir.
The collection was donated by Gladys M. Fitts in 2001.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains memorabilia, 18 items in 10 file folders, all relating to the 1986 reunion for the Class of 1941:
- Book Jacket (1), The 40 Year Cycle, by Ben Austin (Folder 1)
- Card (1), Christmas at Vanderbilt (Folder 2)
- Lyrics (1), Vanderbilt University Alma Mater (Folder 3)
- Lists (5), Members of Vanderbilt A Capella Choir, 1937-38 thru 1941-1942 Lost, Class of 1941, dated October 1985 Class of ’41 Attendees, dated May 1966 Additional Addresses for Vanderbilt A Capella Choir Reunion, May 1986 A Capella Choir, from 1942 Yearbook, page 240 (Folder 4)
- Maps (1), Vanderbilt Campus, 1981 (Folder 5)
- Newsletters (3), Reunion Horizons, Fall 1985 Reunion Horizons, Spring 1986 Reunion Horizons, Summer 1986 (Folder 6)
- Newspaper (1), Vanderbilt Register, May 16, 1986 (Folder 7)
- Photograph (1), A Capellla Choir, 1937-1938 (Folder 8)
- Photograph (1), Campus Scenes – 13 images in booklet [1985] (Folder 9)
- Programs (3), Reunion ‘86 (Folder 10)